That these are our five videos on health insurance
and if you want to understand it very well
then watch the
last four videos, then it will be
easy for you to understand about health insurance and its benefits.
In this video we will talk about that common question that
people often ask. Many people have
this question that whether in our
individual family floater policy, we get
maternity benefit or pregnancy
delivery benefits or can we get it or
not
because often in the corporate policies which
are quality and which your employer has
for you, there is a group policy,
maternity benefits are available in it, except
some exceptions in this policy,
if somewhere we have chosen that we do
not want to take this option, otherwise
in maximum policies maternity benefits are already there, then
this question arises that can all these
benefits be available in our individual family
floater policy, can it be
available in Patel College, many Suraj
companies offer this  There were still
many insurance companies that do
not offer maternity benefits in individual family floater policies. However, there are now
many insurance companies in the market and there is
competition, and they
want to offer benefits to their customers. So, by paying a
small extra premium,
you can also avail maternity benefits
in one of your policies. This becomes
very important for those who are
currently planning to get married or have a child.
If you plan to have a child in the next two to three years,
you should definitely have a
policy that provides birth control cover, provides childcare
benefits, and
ensures that the delivery expenses are
not burdensome to you and the insurance company
bears those expenses. For this, you will have to
contact your insurance company or
discuss whether you want a plan that includes
maternity benefits. However, keep in
mind that insurance
policies often have a waiting period. It is
not that you are pregnant and if you
take out a policy, it may happen.  You will get the benefit at this very time. This will
not happen.
For this, insurance companies have kept a waiting period of one year, two years or
three years. Only when you
cross the waiting period, you
get the benefit if the matter is fine. So, you
need to keep this point in mind. You
need to read your policy document and if you do
not have any benefits at home, then you need to ask for it.
This will be a profitable deal for you. So, if
you like the information, then
maximum people should share this video, so that
4000 people can get its benefit. If you are
on the channel for the first time, then subscribe to the channel
and also press the bell icon button so that
you keep getting such informative videos
first. Thank you.